Diego Raul Rojas Camargo

Peru • Arequipa • devup2332@gmail.com • +51976469908 • https://drojascam.com

Summary

I'm a full stack developer from Peru with over 3 years of experience in frontend and backend development applications.

I always tend to implement the best solution that I find for each task assigned to me having good communication with my work team

Education

San Agustin UniversityBachelor Telecommunications Engineering 2015 - 2019

Peru, Arequipa

Experience

Lapzo Full Stack Engineer Mexico City May 2022 – August 2024

- Maintenance of the main application of the company developed with React, Vitejs, Hasura, Graphql and RadixUI
- During this work I was solving bugs and creating new functionalities for the application both in the backend and in the frontend.
- Creation of differents scripts to solve specific problems in the platform using Nodejs as environment

Inetum Frontend Engineer Peru, Lima

September 2021 – May 2022

- Front End development for an application developed with Nextjs, React, Express, Material UI, ApolloServer and GraphQL.
- A redesign of the application was carried out to manage the company's back office
- A microservices system was developed to manage sales and new product orders.

Jabu Frontend Engineer

Peru, Lima

March 2021 - August 2021

- I was working on a new version of this company's main application with NextJs , Prisma and Typescript
- Something that was taken into account was the optimization of each aspect of the application

Skills

Technical: Javascript | Typescript | Nodejs | React | Nextjs | Nestjs | Redux | React Native | Express

Language: Spanish and English